notionink.com 2013-06-07

# NOTION INK PRIVACY POLICY

                          NOTION INK PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is important to us. We understand the sensitivity of the information you
provide to us and we are committed to protecting the security of this information and your
privacy. Please review this Privacy Policy carefully to learn about how collection and usage
of your data is done by us.
COLLECTING USER INFORMATION
When you visit and use the Notion Ink website or the Notion Ink online store, you agree
that we may collect and use your personal information (such as name, address, phone
number, e-mail, company name, the products you shop for or purchase and any other
information you provide) for specific purposes, including but not limited to, providing the
products and services you purchase from us, marketing, sales, mailing-list, support.
We take user data security seriously and we strive to maintain the proper administrative,
technical and physical measures to safeguard your information against loss, theft and
misuse, as well as any unauthorized disclosure, alteration, destruction, or access. When we
ask for your information, it is done with the intent of improving the relationship between
Notion Ink and you. The information furnished by you may be combined with other data
(from our database) to deliver better products and services.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Notion Ink website or the Notion Ink store and purchase a product or
service, you may be required to share your personal information such as your name, phone
number, email id or address, and your credit card details.
USE OF PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
 1.   We use your personal information for providing assistance in completing your
      transaction or purchase order and to prevent and detect security threats, fraud or
      other potential malicious activity.
 2.   From time to time, we may communicate with you about our products and services.
      You may opt out of such communication at any time by notifying us through email.
 3.   Your personal information may be used to measure the performance of marketing
      initiatives and to help us in improving our services, content, and marketing.
 4.   We may use your personal information to send you important notifications like your
      purchased products or any changes in the company policies at regular intervals in
      future.
 5.   Your personal information can also be used for internal financial or non-financial
      purposes.
 6.   While you use or purchase a product or service from Notion Ink website or online
      store, you may be sharing some non-personal information as well with us such as
      your gender, profession, city, language, zip code, area code, user activities, etc. We
      may use or share this information at any time for any commercial or non-commercial
      purpose.
 7.   We may also collect the data about the traffic at our website or store at various
      sections; this may be done in order to understand the importance of the various
      sections available at our website or store. We consider all this information to be non-
      personal and may use or share this information for commercial or non-commercial
      purposes.
COOKIES
When you visit our website, a small text file may be saved on to your hard drive (a cookie).
It helps us to identify you when you return to our website after some time, or move from
one page to another on our website.
Most browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can usually refuse cookies

or selectively accept cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off
all cookies, there may be some features of our website that will not be available to you,
and some Web pages may not display properly.
At the time you visit our website or online store or in the course of your transaction, we
automatically gather certain information including but not limited to your Internet Protocol
(IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and
exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click-stream data and store it in log
files. The intent of collecting such information is to help us to analyze and understand the
current market trends, for administering our website more effectively, to study your
activities on our website and also to gather region specific information. Notion Ink may use
this information for commercial or non-commercial purposes.
We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal
information, except the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers, which are
treated as personal information. In addition, to the extent that non-personal information is
combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal
information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.
THIRD PARTIES INFORMATION SHARING
Except as provided herein, Notion Ink ensures to its website users that any of their
personal information, collected by us by visits to our website or online store or in the
course of your transaction, shall not be disclosed to any third party without your prior
consent. Notion Ink may disclose or supply such information to any third party which in its
opinion is required to process your request or purchase order or otherwise. Further, Notion
Ink may be obligated to disclose your information when mandated by law, rules and
regulations; for enforcing the terms and conditions governing your use or transaction with
our website or online store; and to safeguard our operations or our website users.
Furthermore, in the event Notion Ink undergoes restructuring including but not limited to
acquisition, merger or sale, then all your information stored with us, whether personal or
non-personal, shall be transferred, as per the applicable laws, to the relevant third party.
We reserve the right to disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances
where we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary or appropriate, such as for the
purposes of national security, to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities,
to protect our rights or property or for other issues of public importance.
INFORMATION SECURITY
Notion Ink takes the trust you place in us seriously. To prevent unauthorized access or
disclosure, to maintain data accuracy and to ensure the appropriate use of the information,
Notion Ink utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to
safeguard the information we collect.
We do not receive or get access to your credit card or similar financial information while
you purchase products at the Notion Ink website or store. The transaction is handled at the
secure website or our payment processing partner, CCAvenue, which has obtained PCI
DSS 1.1 certification for its data security. You may review their privacy policy at
https://www.ccavenue.com/includes/privacy_policies.jsp.
No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result,
while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the
security of any information you transmit to us or from our website, and therefore, you use
our website at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we endeavor to ensure
its security on our systems. We also cannot be responsible for criminal acts of third parties,
such as "hackers", who may seek to compromise our security measures through unlawful
means. Industry-accepted security measures have been integrated into the design,
implementation, and day-to-day operation of the Site.
UNDERAGE USERS
Any user, below 18 years of age (minors), is not eligible to use our website. If you are a
minor, please do not submit any personal information through our websites. As per our
policy, minors cannot sell, purchase or raise request for any product on our website. If you
wish to purchase or sell a product on the website or store such purchase or sale may only
be made by your legal guardian or parents on your behalf.

CHANGES AND INQUIRIES
We may change, modify or withdraw our Privacy Policy, as stated herein, at any time
without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Policy here, with
an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our Policy, we may notify you
by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page. If you
ever have questions regarding this Policy or want to be removed from a mailing list, please
contact us at info@notionink.com.
Notion Ink website: www.notionink.com
Copyright © 2010 Notion Ink Design Labs Pvt. Ltd. All rights reserved.
Privacy v1.0
